Hello friends, today we are going to talk
about the advances in car insurance. In the last video, I had
explained in detail about first party insurance and third party insurance.
In the last video, I had mentioned
how you would know by looking at your policy whether
it is first party insurance or
third party insurance. I had explained it by giving an
example. I am providing the link of the video
in the description, which you
can go and watch. Let's go and talk
about advances in vehicle insurance. The most commonly used ad in the insurance sector is
zero
depression. It is called bumper-to-bumper cover or
sleep cover because if it is
taken and you make any kind of
claim, then there is
no depression of any kind in it, you
get complete clearance there, that is why they
call it 200 position cover. This is normal. No, the
paper is wasted only for 5 years, after that
many insurance companies do not offer it.
If you are planning to buy a new car, then
you should take JIO depression.
After that there is 24*7 roadside assistance.
This means that  If your car
is running on the road and there is any such problem in the car
like the tyres of your car get flat
or there is any kind of problem in the engine or battery,
then you can
call the insurance company and get help from there.
If you have taken 824 into seven roadside
assistance, which is admin, that is
engine protrusion cover. This means that
if water gets into the engine or if the engine
seizes due to oil leak in the engine, if you have taken this protrusion, then
you can quote any kind of expense in it,
you do not need to pay any money in it.
After that is
entry protector no claim bonus. This
means that if you have taken a huge policy, even if
you make any kind of claim in it,
you will get the next year 2nd, there will be
no deduction of any kind in it, you will get the full entry there.
In this, it is called all these protectors.
After that is lock replacement.
This means that if the key of your car gets
stolen, in that case, if the
lock of your car is changed.  If you have
taken this cover, then whatever
expense is incurred in it, you get the full money for it.
If you have taken this cover,
after that the small don is
consumables. If
every vehicle meets with an accident, the
repairing is done in it or many types of passes are
put in place at that time, the nuts and bolts that fall,
both of these are gone * done, all these
consumables come under it. If you have found this, then
you do not need to pay any money for it. In
normal insurance, you have to pay for the
expenses that happen,
but if you have found this, then
its express is
also covered in it.
After that, the admin is add aliens. It
means that if your vehicle
meets with an accident and it goes for repair, during that
period, if you have to
hire a vehicle, the money incurred for that is
covered under navy alarms.
If you have taken this, then whatever
you feel like a friend, the insurance
company will pay for it, after that comes the
invoice price.  The meaning of invoice price is
that when you buy a new car, let's say
you have bought a new car in 10 lakhs,
but when an insurance company insures it, then it
decides the insurance by deducting some money from it, for example, if
your new car is worth 10 lakhs, then the
insurance company
will insure you only for Rs. 9.5 lakhs.
If you have taken the invoice price, at that
time if your car meets with an accident,
that is the total loss, then
you have been offered an idea of ​​what happens in normal conditions,
but if you have taken the invoice price, then the
money you have to buy the car at this price, plus the RTO and
road accident chances that you have given,
you will get it in full, if you have
taken the invoice price in don't.
Last of all is the personal accident cover, that is personal
accident cover, in this, if the car meets with an accident
due to which the owner dies or there is
any kind of debt, in that case, the
amount which is predefined in the policy,
that amount is given to his nominee
and apart from this  According to the seating capacity of the vehicle, you
can take VPN cover for the remaining passengers. Today I have
told you about almost all the addons, still if you have
any kind of doubt
then you can definitely ask me in the comment box,
which I will definitely reply to. Thank you lovingly from the
bottom of my heart for staying connected with me.